[
    {
        "question": "E2 on string 1",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "F2 on string 1",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "F#2 on string 1",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "G2 on string 1",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "G#2 on string 1",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "A2 on string 1",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "A#2 on string 1",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "B2 on string 1",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "C3 on string 1",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "C#3 on string 1",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "D3 on string 1",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "D#3 on string 1",
        "answer": "11"
    }	
]
